<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IPPTReady</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string-array name="information_name">
        <item>Guidelines</item>
        <item>Passing Criteria</item>
        <item>Failing/Defaulting</item>
        <item>Exemption</item>
        <item>IPPT Test Stations</item>
        <item>Scoring/Calculation</item>
        <item>Awards/Incentives</item>
        <item>Location/Schedules</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="information_description">
        <item>IPPT requirements and window</item>
        <item>Passing criteria for the IPPT</item>
        <item>What happens if you fail or default on your IPPT</item>
        <item>Exemptions from IPPT</item>
        <item>The three stations that IPPT consists of</item>
        <item>Scoring and Calculation for IPPT</item>
        <item>Potential awards and incentives you can receive from taking your IPPT</item>
        <item>IPPT locations and timings</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="information_details">
        <item>IPPT is a mandatory annual (within a 12-month period, i.e. your IPPT window)
            requirement for all eligible NSmen with PES A, B/ B1/ B2/ C1 status. Your first IPPT
            window starts on your birthday after your Operationally Ready Date (ORD) and ends a day
            before your next birthday. </item>
        <item>You need to take and pass your annual IPPT within your IPPT window. The IPPT
            comprises 3 stations – Push-Ups, Sit-Ups and 2.4km Run. To pass, you need to score a
            minimum of 1 point in each station, and achieve a total score of at least 51 out of
            100 points. The IPPT scoring system is calibrated to your age, and you will receive
            different incentive awards depending on the total score.</item>
        <item>If you fail your IPPT, you may retake it multiple times within your IPPT window.
            Once your current IPPT window has closed and you still have not passed your IPPT, you
            will need to complete 10 sessions of mandatory NS Fitness Improvement Training (FIT)
            in your next IPPT window. If you are not exempted and did not take your annual IPPT
            within your IPPT window, you will be considered an IPPT defaulter. You will be called
            back for investigation and may be subjected to disciplinary action. In addition, you
            are required to complete 10 mandatory NS FIT sessions in your next window.</item>
        <item>You can be exempted from your annual fitness requirements once you have been
            disrupted from your Operationally Ready National Service (ORNS) duties.</item>
        <item>To measure the major components of physical fitness, your IPPT will consist of
            3 stations. Push-Ups, Sit-Ups and 2.4km Run.</item>
        <item>You will earn points that are calibrated to your age group at each IPPT station.
            These age groups are adjusted within 3-year bands.</item>
        <item>NSmen who achieve a gold award for their IPPT receive $500, $300 for a silver award,
            and $200 for a pass with incentive.</item>
        <item>You can take your IPPT at any of the FCCs that best suits your schedule. Reporting
            time is 15 minutes before each IPPT session, i.e. 1645 hrs / 1845hrs for the weekday
            session and 0715 hrs / 1645 hrs / 1745 hrs for the Saturday session respectively.</item>
    </string-array>

    <color name="whitesmoke">#F5F5F5</color>
</resources>